8coupons.com 2007-12-29

# 8coupons.com - Privacy Policy

**_8COUPONS INC. Privacy Policy_**

8coupons inc. (“8coupons” or “our”, “us” or “we”) understands that its customers, visitors, users, and others who use [www.8coupons.com](http://www.8coupons.com/) or other websites owned or operated by 8coupons (collectively or individually “Users” or “you”) value their privacy. This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the 8coupons Website (as hereinafter defined). 8coupons provides this Privacy Policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the Website.

**Effective Date.**

The most recent version of this Privacy Policy is effective as of July 16, 2007.

**Privacy Policy.**

This Privacy Policy applies to 8coupons and/or other affiliated Websites or entities controlled by, or under common control with and through 8coupons (each such Website being individually referred to herein as the “Website”). 8coupons respects the privacy of its users, and this Privacy Policy details the information that is collected on our Website and how such information is used by 8coupons. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. In addition, please review the Terms of Use posted at our Website, which governs your use of the Website. Your use of the Website indicates to us that you have read and accepted our privacy practices, as outlined in this Privacy Policy and in our Terms of Use.  Finally your use of the Website and any personal information you provide on the Website remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.

Please note that any video, image, or other content posted at the direction of Users onto the Website becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy.

**Applicability.**

This Privacy Policy only applies to Websites owned and/or operated by or for 8coupons, and upon which 8coupons has placed a “link” which, when “clicked”, transfers you to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy only covers information collected at this Website, and does not cover any information collected by any other Website (unless otherwise specifically stated or disclosed by 8coupons), its corporate affiliates, licensees or any other company.

**Disclosure of Information.**

  1. Personally Identifiable Information: You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, birth date or e-mail address and referred to in this Privacy Policy as “PI”) to 8coupons when choosing to participate in various activities on the Website such as uploading videos, posting reviews in our forums, message board, or in the video comments section if applicable, entering contests or sweepstakes, taking advantage of promotions, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists.  Generally, you may browse our Website without providing us with PI. However, there may be times when we ask you to provide us with certain PI, such as when you choose to register with our Website. We may also ask you to provide us with demographic information or information regarding your interests, hobbies or similar information to enhance your online experience. 8coupons reserves the right, at any time, to modify, alter or add features to our Website that require you to register or otherwise provide additional PI or to require registration to access our Website. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you may not be able to participate in or view some of the Website’s features. 8coupons does not sell, rent or share PI collected with other people other than that specifically described herein.
  2. Underage users:  The Website does not knowingly collect PI from children under thirteen (13) years of age.  This is not a Website directed to children under the age of 13, therefore, 8coupons does not knowingly collect any information from children under 13 years of age at the Website. If you are under 13 years of age, do not send any information about yourself to 8coupons. If we discover that a child under the age of 13 has provided the Website with PI, we will delete that child’s PI from its system.
  3. Anonymous Information: When you visit the Website, our web servers automatically collect website usage information. Website usage information is anonymous information that describes how our visitors use and navigate our Website, and it includes the number and frequency of visitors to each web page, video and the time-span of their stays. 8coupons collects the anonymous information automatically sent to us by your web browser, referrer data that identifies the web page visited prior and subsequent to visiting our Website, and IP address. We may also determine what technology is available through your browser in order to serve you the most appropriate version of a web page.
  4. Log File Information: When visitors call for pages from our Website, our servers log the visitor’s IP address. 8coupons may collect IP addresses for a range of internal purposes, such as system administration, to report aggregate information to our business partners or to review the number of visits to different pages or videos watched on our Website.
  5. Cookies Information: When you visit the Website, 8coupons may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. 8coupons does not store any PI in cookies, but it may link the cookie to any information it collects. You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers, which is standard in the Internet industry. 8coupons does not control these cookies, and these cookies are not subject to our Privacy Policy. Visitors to our Website should check the Privacy Policy of the advertiser to determine how it uses cookies. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of our Website may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.
  6. Clear GIFs Information: When you use the Website, 8coupons may employ “clear GIFs” which are used to track the online usage patterns of our Users anonymously (i.e., in a non-personally-identifiable manner). In addition, we may also use clear GIFs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients.

**Use of Information.**

  1. If you submit PI to 8coupons through the Website, then we may employ your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Website.  We may also use your PI to contact you regarding your use of our Website or changes to our Privacy Policy, Terms of Use or other notices or terms that affect you and your use of our Website.  If you e-mail someone else a review or other special feature from our Website, 8coupons may use the information you provide about someone else to send that person the requested e-mail.
  2. Any PI or content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.
  3. 8coupons may not use your email address or other PI to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Website changes or for customer service purposes).
  4. 8coupons may use both your PI and certain non-personally-identifiable information to improve the quality and design of the Website and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends.
  5. 8coupons may use cookies, clear gifs, and log file PI to: (a) retain information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Website; (b) supply custom, personalized content and information; (c) examine the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests.
  6. 8coupons may employ other trusted companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include analyzing data, providing marketing assistance and providing customer service. Such third parties may have access to our Users’ PI in order to provide these services to us on our behalf solely for such purposes; however, they are not permitted to use it for any other purpose.
  7. 8coupons may not rent, sell or otherwise disclose your PI to third parties unless disclosed herein or at the time such information is collected or unless you otherwise give consent, other than in the following limited circumstances:
    1. Legal Action: 8coupons may disclose information about its users, including PI, when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Website and applicable state and federal laws, or to protest against misuse or unauthorized use of our Website. We may also disclose user PI whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to limit our legal liability, to protect or defend our rights or property or protect the safety, rights or property of our users.  We also reserve the right to disclose PI and/or non-personally-identifiable information that 8coupons believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce the Terms of Use
    2. Corporate Change: 8coupons may sell, transfer or otherwise disclose user information, including PI, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, the sale of substantially all assets, or other fundamental corporate change respecting the Website.

**Security.**

  1. You may decline to submit personally identifiable information through the Website, in which case 8coupons may not be able to provide certain services to you. Please note that media files uploaded by Users to the Website cannot be removed and remain subject to our Terms of Use.
  2. 8coupons takes steps to secure the data you submit to us, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to our user data. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be one hundred percent secure. Therefore, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to 8coupons, and you do so at your own risk.

**  
**

**Consent to Transfer.**

The Website is hosted in the United States and is intended for and directed to Users in the United States. If you are a User accessing the Website from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Website, which are governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

**Acceptance/Changes to Privacy Policy**

By using the Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 8coupons reserves the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time in its sole discretion. We will post any changes here; therefore, please continue to check back from time to time. However, we will only use the PI you provide to the Website in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy, unless you give us your consent.

**Third-party Advertisers.**

  1. 8coupons permits other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to deliver advertisements within the Website. They may also use other tools to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize advertising content.
  2. As noted above, 8coupons does not provide any PI to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. However, please note that if 8coupons is requested by an advertiser to show an advertisement to a certain audience and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may determine that you fit the profile of the audience it is trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the Website, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any PI), to calculate which ads it should send to you.
  3. If you are concerned with the use of your non personal information by these third party advertisers, you should consult their respective privacy policies for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. 8coupons’s Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or Websites.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at the address provided on the Website from which you “clicked” via an authorized link to arrive at this Privacy Policy.  If you’d like to contact us about our Privacy Policy, please email us at: business_support[AT]8coupons.com.
